radarsync.com 2002-12-06

# RadarSync Privacy Statement

| 

**[ ](http://www.radarsync.com/)RadarSync Privacy Statement**

**RADARSYNC has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website,<http://www.radarsync.com/>, and for our RadarSync messaging.**

 **

RadarSync will never share information about you without your permission (unless required by law). 

RadarSync will never compromise your online privacy. 

RadarSync never requires you to give us any personal information to visit our Websites, or to use our software products. Since we don't have any personal information your anonymity and privacy are guaranteed. 

RadarSync does not require that you accept cookies to visit our Websites, or to use our software products.

RadarSync does not sell or reveal your personal information (we don't have it) to any of our partners or other third parties. 

RadarSync does not create user profiles.

WEB SITE: www.RadarSync.com

**

> Our RadarSync website does not collect information about visitors.

**RadarSync Desktop Client.**

> RadarSync regularly contacts RadarSync's and your device manufacturer's update servers to check if newer versions of RadarSync, device drivers, or pre-installed software updates are available. If newer versions are available, RadarSync will notify the user and give the user the option to upgrade. The user has the ability to disable the update check at any time. Instructions for disabling this feature can be found at RadarSync.com for [Windows](http://www.radarsync.com/techsupport/uninstall.html) versions of the software and in RadarSync Options menu. No personal information whatsoever is transmitted back to RadarSync or device manufacturers during these processes. 

**RadarSync Information Broadcasting Features**

> **Product Offers  
> ** From time to time, RadarSync may broadcast product offers or promotions from your manufacturer. These advertisements and offers are targeted based on your computer information (type, features, upgrade needs), but not based on any personal information about you. Users have the option of configuring RadarSync so that they do not receive these product offers and promotions.
> 
> From time to time, some of RadarSync's advertising will only be applicable to certain geographic regions (phone services, insurance providers, etc). In such cases, RadarSync will use the user's IP address to send the most appropriate advertising. Many IP addresses are commonly associated with Internet service providers, universities, or major corporations in specific regions or localities. The only information used in this procedure is the data about the geographic region from which the user's computer is contacting the Internet. Absolutely no personal information (email address, address of residence, demographics, etc.) is revealed to RadarSync, your product manufactuer, or our advertisers in these situations.

**Updates to this Privacy Statement  
** While we will never change our fundamental commitment to protecting user privacy, regulatory changes or other circumstances may require us to modify this Privacy Statement. In the event that we do amend this Statement, we will post the amended Statement on our website at http://www.radarsync.com/legal/RadarSyncPrivacyStatement.htm, and the amended Statement will be effective 15 days after it is first posted.

**Contacting the Web Site  
** If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact our [webmaster.](mailto:webmaster@radarsync.com)

Last updated 01/01/2002
